



BIOGRAPHY

FROM SUNNY SAN DIEGO, I'M A 22 YEAR OLD TECH ARTIST RECENTLY GRADUATED AT UCSD. ALONG MY LIFE AND STUDIES, I HAVE BEEN INSPIRED BY MY PASSION FOR THE ARTS. I AM GROUNDED IN SOFTWARE AND PROGRAMMING, IMPLEMENTING AUDIOVISUAL MEDIA, HUMAN INTERACTION, DATA VISUALIZATION, PERFORMANCE, AND ONLINE VIDEO GAME CULTURE INTO MY PROJECTS.

PASSIONS











EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA - SAN DIEGO
 ELEANOR ROOSEVELT COLLEGE | SEP 2015 - JUNE 2019

MAJOR: INTERDISCIPLINARY COMPUTING AND THE ARTS (B.A.)

EMPHASIS: COMPUTER SCIENCE GPA: 3.65

SAN MARCOS HIGH SCHOOL
SAN MARCOS, CA | SEP 2011 - JUN 2015

EXCALIBUR KNIGHTS: TOP 3% OF

GRADUATING CLASS

EXPERIENCE

QUALCOMM INSTITUTE: CALIT2
 UCSD | APR 2017 - JUNE 2017

STUDENT ASSISTANT: INDEPENDENTLY ARCHIVED UC SAN DIEGO ON-CAMPUS EVENTS WITH DSLR CAMERA EQUIPMENT. ASSISTED IN POST-EDITING PROCESS VIA ADOBE LIGHTROOM SOFTWARE.

THE DESIGN LAB @ UCSD UCSD | UCSD | FEB 2017 - MAY 2017

STUDENT ASSISTANT: INDEPENDENTLY ASSISTED IN DESIGN LAB DAILY DUTIES AND ONLINE FILE SYSTEM. ORGANIZED, DEVELOPED, AND ARCHIVED MEDIA AS THE LAB'S NEEDS.

PHOTOGRAPHY / VIDEOGRAPHY FREELANCE | MAR 2014 -

PERSONAL EVENTS & WEDDINGS: PLANNED A FINAL PRODUCT FOR CLIENTS' NEEDS ON MULTIPLE OCCASIONS. ENSURED PROPER SETUP OF EQUIPMENT IN ADAPTABLE ENVIRONMENTS ACCORDING TO SCHEDULE. RECORDED, EDITED, AND PROCESSED PHOTO AND VIDEO WITH ADOBE SOFTWARE.

RITA'S ITALIAN ICE
CARLSBAD, CA | FEB 2015 - SEP 2015

TREAT TEAM LEAD: SUPERVISED NEW HIRES IN DAILY TASKS: MANAGE THE STOREFRONT, LOG INVENTORY, AND REPORT DAILY SALES. OVERSAW REMOTE CATERING EVENTS.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

PREMIERE PRO

AFTER EFFECTS

UNIX	
JAVA	•
PYTHON	
С	
PURE DATA	
BLENDER	
UNITY	
OW WORKSHOP	
PHOTOSHOP	
LIGHTROOM	

PORTFOLIO

- PIXELMON
 - 2D TILE-BASED MAP ADVENTURE GAME, DEVELOPED USING PYTHON AND PYGAME ON A RASPBERRY PI3
- HUMAN MUSIC, ROBOTS DANCE
 3D OSCILLOSCOPE AUDIOVISUAL INTERACTIVE PERFORMANCE
 USING AN XBOX KINECT WITH BLENDER, PYTHON, AND PURE DATA
- CODEPENDENTS COLLECTIVE: TOXIC ONLINE RELATIONSHIPS

LIVE-STREAMED PERFORMANCE COMBINING LIVE VIDEOGAME COMMUNITIES & CHATROOMS WITH AN AUDIOVISUAL EXPERIENCE

